<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>huawei on Dennis Kruyt</title>
    <link>https://kruyt.org/tags/huawei/</link>
    <description>Recent content in huawei on Dennis Kruyt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 22:20:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kruyt.org/tags/huawei/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Huawei FAT WLAN Access Points in Grafana</title>
      <link>https://kruyt.org/huawei-fat-wlan-access-points-in-grafana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 22:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kruyt.org/huawei-fat-wlan-access-points-in-grafana/</guid>
      <description>With Huawei Enterprise Access points you have different firmware versions for different deployment scenarios. A FIT version for when you have an Wireless Access Controller (AC). This AC will managed all your AP and you have metrics available from within the AC. Huawei also offers a FAT version of the firmware for the AP. This is an standalone verion and there is no central management and overview of your AP&amp;rsquo;s with the FAT version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei Dorado all flash metrics in Grafana</title>
      <link>https://kruyt.org/huawei-dorado-all-flash-metrics-in-grafana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 21:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kruyt.org/huawei-dorado-all-flash-metrics-in-grafana/</guid>
      <description>Recently I got my hands on a nice all flash storage from Huawei, the Dorado 5000. Off course I wanted to see if my Grafana dashboard I created for the Huawei Oceanstor series was also working on the Dorado, most is working, but some mibs are different and not all performance metrics that are availble on the Oceanstor are on the Dorado. So I adjusted the Telegraf and Grafana dashboard to work correclty with the Dorado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huawei OceanStor metrics in Grafana</title>
      <link>https://kruyt.org/oceanstor_grafana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 19:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kruyt.org/oceanstor_grafana/</guid>
      <description>I manage a couple of storages at work. I got a few Huawei OceanStor storages. v2 as wel v3 storages. There is some commercial tooling from Huawei available to gather metrics, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t fit my needs. I found out that all or almost all metrics that I need are available via SNMP. So it was not hard to setup a Grafana dashboard with all metrics.
Pre install Make sure you have installed InfluxDB as the time-series database Telegraf as the collector first.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
